luxuryhotelsguides.com 2019-07-20

# Luxury Hotels Guides | Manage Booking & About Us

**Privacy Policy**

 **Gathering of Information**

This policy relates to nformation gathered from this site. Our site does not gather personally identifiable information about any individual except when knowingly provided by such individual. For example, we may ask you for information when you register for our newsletter or signup to our site services. You always have the option not to provide the information we request. If you choose not to provide the information we request, you can still visit most of the Web site, but you may be unable to access certain options and services. 

**Cookies **

Third Party advertisers may set cookies to track user information within our Web Site - we do not purposefully gather this information.

Please be aware that our sponsors, advertisers or Web sites that have links on our site may collect personally identifiable information about you. The information practices of those parties and Web sites linked to are not covered by this privacy statement. 

**Browser Level Information **

Our website collects not identifying geographical and IP level information from users browsers for website statistics and aggregate reporting purposes only. This information is not disclosed in a granular format. 

**Use of Information **

Our primary goal in collecting user information is to enhance your experience on our Web site. We achieve this goal by, among other things, providing newsletters to the e-mail address that you may in turn specify.

When you are on an area of our site and are asked for personal information, you are sharing that information with our Web Site as well as any business partners providing hosting and other services. If you do not want your information to be shared, you can choose not to allow the transfer of your information by not using that particular service. These parties, as well as advertisers who contract directly with a third-party service to serve their advertisements, may set their own cookies. 

In addition, any personally identifiable information provided by our users as part of an advertiser promotion online may be provided directly to advertisers. 

If you have any questions regarding our privacy statement, please feel free to contact us by email. 

This statement may change from time to time , so please check back regularly.

_Contact us today -_

**[ [email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection#f98a8c8989968b8db991968d9c958a9e8c909d9c8ad7979c8d) **
